<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HParker</title><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on HParker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.hparker.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/art/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/art/</guid><description>Art</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/bf3d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/bf3d/</guid><description>BF3D Demo Video | Code Pending..
_Video depicting a Bf3d program running as it fills in a diamond shaped 3d shape on the screen_ Bf3d is a simple esoteric programming language inspired by BrainFuck and like languages. Bf3d uses the same basic syntax as BrainFuck, but replaces + and - with R G and B which increment colors and r g b to decrement a color. Also, because the program works in 3 dimensions, the program can move the cursor left and right with &amp;gt; and &amp;lt; like usual, but the cursor can also move up and down with ^ and v.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/emulators/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/emulators/</guid><description>Emulators page</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/projects/</guid><description>Projects Ruby Explorer Explore how ruby parses your code and what instructions it generates easily in your browser
Ruby Todo Ruby.wasm todo list in your browser with editable code.
Puzzle Engine An alterative implementation of the puzzlescript language interpreter and runtime using C and SDL. A large number of puzzles work, but not everything is supported properly.
BF3D My Novel Esoteric programming language based on BrainFuck, but in 3d with beautiful 8-bit colors</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/puzzle-engine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/puzzle-engine/</guid><description>puzzle engine Demo Video | Code | Inspiration
This video shows the PuzzleEngine test suite running through the tests with the optional renderer attached to show the puzzles being sovled at comically fast speeds.
PuzzleEngine is a PuzzleScript interpreter that allows you to run PuzzleScript games on your computer instead of in a web browser. You can find and play PuzzleScript games on puzzlescript.net.
Technical Details The parser uses flex and bison to lex and parse the program.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/ruby-explorer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/ruby-explorer/</guid><description>Ruby Explorer GitHub | Site
Ruby Explorer makes it easy to explore and share Ruby VM internals. Typing Ruby code into Ruby Explorer generates a list of VM instructions created by ruby with links to their implementation in Ruby&amp;rsquo;s source code. In addition you can see what tokens the lexer returned and the S-Expression that ruby generated from those tokens.
I became interested in making this tool while reading Ruby Under A Microscope by AUTHOR.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.hparker.xyz/signal-state-run-identifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.hparker.xyz/signal-state-run-identifier/</guid><description>Signal State Run Identifier Steam Workshop Page
My user created level on Signal state for identifying runs of numbers.</description></item></channel></rss>